http://www.fibercore.com/about-us/certificates-policies

Certificates &amp; Policies
Fibercore is committed to excellence, efficiency, & safetyFibercore has implemented a fully integrated set of management systems covering Quality, Environmental, and Health & Safety.Quality: ISO 9001:2015Fibercore is dedicated to supplying customers with exceptional quality products, service, and support. Certified to ISO9001, Fibercore maintain traceability to all critical elements and materials in all the fiber that is manufactured. Unique identification of every length of fiber ensures that all test and manufacturing data can be easily accessed.Fully documented procedures and instructions provide consistency and uniformity of products. Controlled test plans implemented through calibrated equipment guarantees the fiber is matched to your process.Quality Management CertificateQuality PolicyConflict Mineral StatementEnvironment: ISO 14001:2015Fibercore is committed to reducing its environmental impact, be this through the prevention of pollution or the reduction of resource and energy use. An ISO14001 certified management system was installed by in-house staff to manage all aspects of Fibercore’s environmental management including the environmental permit under which Fibercore operates.Environmental PolicyEnvironmental Management CertificateHealth & Safety: OHSAS 18001:2007Fibercore extends its commitment to staff, visitors, and neighbors by the addition of the Occupational Health & Safety Management System to our procedures. Work is underway to transition to the new standard ISO 45001:2018 and this is scheduled to be in place by June 2020.Occupational Health & Safety CertificateHealth & Safety PolicyRelated Regulatory RequirementsRoHS & REACHOur products all comply with RoHS requirements and with REACH.RoHS statementREACH StatementPrivacy Policy & GDPRHere at Fibercore we take your privacy seriously and will only use your personal information to administer your account and to provide the products and services you have requested from us. We will never sell personal data to 3rd parties.Privacy Policy Applicant Privacy NoticeWith your agreement, we will hold your resume/CV for up to six months, and you can see how we look after your data in our Applicant Privacy Notice.Applicant Privacy NoticeModern Slavery StatementModern Slavery Statement
Main
Products
Services & Support
Industries & Applications
Perspectives
About Us
Contact Us & Locations
History
